there was a black man sitting at a desk
directly to your right look at him
Morpheus side his arrow guy needs a
stapler I can't find that I worked at a
couple of fast state places parked cars
at wrestling I couldn't pay the rent and
I was too ashamed to go home that's what
I meant it
she was a hooker I made it sound so
great okay
you gotta get two out of here
[Applause]
Molly Molly Molly hey mom
your husband's clothes fit funny girl
well they look better on you than they
ever did on him why don't you take them
off mm-hmm ready to get some of this 11
you bet your ass I am
my dumbass husband is dead not me you
ready to step into the jungle oh man you
know I see
yeah I'm looking right at you there goes
that's it
you're freaking me you like to watch
more watch how does it make you feel
and if I could just slide a finger down
a crack of that is how my boys could see
this look at the
that's over that I want to have doggy
style sex with her Alba hurt in the net
[Music]
[Applause]
hello hello eyo do you know who this is
Orpheus yes I've been looking for you
Neil I don't know if you're ready to see
what I want to show you but
unfortunately you and I have run out of
time they're coming for you neo and I
don't know what they're going to do
who's coming for me stand up and see for
yourself
[Music]
I can guide you out of there but you
must do exactly as I say okay
the cubicle across from me was empty
go now
[Music]
stay there
when I tell you go to the end of the
hall stay as low as you can now
[Music]
[Applause]
there's a black man sitting at a desk
directly to your right look at him more
fees cite his arrow guy needs a stapler
I can't find that hello dum-dum do you
think this is dude you totally got me
[Applause]
[Laughter]
please be seated
hello America as you all know there's an
asteroid the size of Maine speeding
towards Earth as we speak I'd like to
take a moment out of the day to address
the allegations that this is somehow my
fault firstly I'd like to say that these
allegations are absolutely in 100% false
secondly and most importantly I'd like
to say that you must disgust me
you've got damn right I said it if you
do just one of the things I was sworn to
secrecy to you would buckle under the
goddamn pressure how about this I have
here in my hand to kill for AIDS we've
had this for 25 years
have a great weekend get out shopping
are you crazy yet well I have someone
I'd like you to meet come on up here
Polo America I'd like you to meet my
good friend Paula and he is Paula again
and here's Paula one more time we cloned
these three in a laboratory in
Seattle
not only that we added a pinch of black
gene so that they could do things like
this hit it girls thank you very much
all right baby
Oh hold on Paula kill fades sorry about
last night
freaked out yet have I blown your mind
or you think you can still handle my job
because if you're cocky you think that
you got hold of this I got some more
information for you would you like to
know who killed Kennedy ready for the
truth America here it comes
Oswald killed Kennedy that's right Lee
Harvey Oswald killed John F Kennedy
alone and by himself with a magic bullet
that's right the bullet was actually
magical magic does exist we've known
about this for some 2,000 years
I've really owned a Roven I don't care
because the world's gonna end any day
now so I might as well introduce you to
a good friend of mine Bibble Bibble come
on up America this is Bibble Bibble is a
space creature that lives very far away
in a galaxy called Nebulon v and he is
solely responsible for the wave of
Technology we've seen over the last few
decades cell phones pagers playstation 1
& 2 you might think as if the Japanese
were responsible but anyone in the know
knows that it was Bibble for shizzle and
all Bob Bibble cuz only if it's over a
Bibble is a spaceship ready you ready to
get out okay me and bivolo about to
leave but before we go I just want to
say there's no hope for the planet Earth
there's no way to stop the asteroid and
you're all gonna die everyone except for
me and of course Bibble who's been so
kind to let me accompany him on his
spaceship and I'm bringing those three
clone white women with me goodbye
America I hope you all die a fiery death
when the meteor hits next Tuesday come
on babe with us get out of here
[Applause]
what's a love of stretching you know
pulling the old addage big boobs bad
back yeah all set I'm really worried I
didn't have a clean sports bra so I had
to wear a regular one
you'll be fine let's go
don't worry she'll I'm sure nobody
notices really look at that yeah
her presumes are like bouncing around
and everything they're not talking about
you sweet Jesus did you see the jugs on
that brunette I'm gonna go in it's okay
it's not okay stupid boobs nothing but
an inconvenience I wish I didn't have
him
[Music]
careful what you wish for Who I am is
not important but what you said about
those titties yes follow me
Susy hey that's me and that's Frank him
and resources man in my office
he's always slobbering over me not today
so that's why I think I'm qualified for
the promotion yeah well we'll see why is
he being so dismissive what happened to
my boots oh you just answered your own
question
Tim bubbies is gone girl just like he
wished for how did it go not well that
woman was a flat-chested bore okay will
never respond to her for pete's sake
she's got no melons so should I tell her
she's not getting the promotion yes in
fact tell that titlis freak she's fired
Oh guys really like that he's always
been so helpful to me such a loyal
friend hey buddy I have a painting I
need to hang up in my bedroom do you
think you could help Wow I didn't even
know we were buddies I always thought it
was your personal handyman because
you're constantly asking me for favors
that I don't want to do know what you
need a new set of titties and a
boyfriend you'd be all set all right
well it's not what's gotten into him as
much as it is what's gotten out of you
by that of course I mean your massive
milk bladders oh wait I still have big
boobs you can't see you we'll see about
that he can't see you but my black ass
got 20/20 you men are the worst you're
right
oh my gosh surely you are right women
the fairer sex they would never ever
judge another womb by the size of her
boobies now would they
Mazel Tov hey hey wait those are my
friend Oh where's Sheila wasn't she
supposed to be a bridesmaid no I was
gonna have a p1 then I thought am I
getting bridesmaids starting an
itty-bitty titty committee
oh how could she do that
your friends are
besides Sheila even girls love girls
with huge tats especially with
we friends don't have somebody sleeping
head no idea these things were soon
great Oh keep it real girl them things
of lifesavers
listen I'm gonna put this on you but the
fate of the world you hear me the world
rest on them chesticles
[Laughter]
he's lived next door to you know
masturbating to you and those giant cans
Leo's was all he had to live for once it
took that away losses oh you should have
thought about that before you wish them
sweet tits away we're gonna hit it about
ten seconds which is just enough time to
suck a teddy bear
hey in Selah
you've taught me a valuable lesson today
I'm never going to curse my fun bags
again in fact I might even get implants
all right do you listen world
I've got humongo knockers and thanks
mister you must be an angel or something
angel I know angel I'm a day.another
and how did you show me all those places
I am high on PCP now who are you I'm
just bitter
titties have a good day miss
[Music]
so pale
let's start the show
[Music]